### **BENJAMIN WARNER**

#### Computer Science Student

\$\square\$ 289-404-1840 @ benrwarner1@gmail.com

#### **SUMMARY**

A dynamic individual with experience and knowledge of computer hardware and computer languages such as Python, Java, C++, GIT, web development languages (Html, JavaScript, CSS) as well as experience using Linux command line. Has excellent oral and written communication skills as well as patience and self-control. An analytical and creative thinker who clearly identifies problems in order to implement solutions that are in line with operational requirements. Works well in a fast-paced, high-pressure environment and adapts quickly to new situations while adhering to time constraints.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Floor Worker 2022 - Present

The Beer Store

Brooklin, ON

- Responsible for closing and opening tasks such as sweeping and mopping, making a till, and making sure the store looks presentable for the customers and the staff scheduled the following morning
- Responsible for requesting identification from customers to ensure the sale of alcohol is being executed legally and appropriately
- Ensure incoming shipments are accurately and efficiently stocked on the shelves and stored in the back
- Responsible for handling the money in my till for each shift (ie. balancing, collecting, and storing the money)

Server/Bartender 2023 - Present

The Wismer House

Port Elgin, ON

- Created a welcoming and positive environment to make diners and guests feel at home
- Maintained a robust knowledge of several food and drink items to proactively up-sell menu items to guests while ensuring customer satisfaction
- Acted as a team player, and helped bar or service staff depending on which side of the house was busiest
- Maintained impeccably clean workstations by demonstrating attention to detail and a sense of urgency

#### Shift Supervisor/Team Member

2019 - 2022

**Tim Hortons** 

Brooklin, ON

- Maintained a safe environment for guests and co-workers to reduce the risk of injury and accidents
- Investigated and resolved customer inquiries and complaints in an empathetic manner, resolving appropriately
- Developed highly empathetic client relationships and earned a reputation for exceeding service standard goals
- Met all customer call guidelines including service levels, handling time and productivity

#### Camp Counselor

03/2019 - 09/2019

Unifor

Port Elgin, ON

- Worked as a member of a team with the ability to accomplish tasks with little direct supervision further supporting the positive image of the Unifor brand
- Ensured that the site was kept clean, organized, and free of litter to ensure a safe environment and functionality of the facilities
- Assisted in maintaining accurate program records including incident reports, logbook documentation, and daily attendance.

#### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Science, Computer Science

2022 - Present

Ontario Tech University (3rd Year)

Oshawa, ON

High School (Honor Roll)

2018 - 2022

**Brooklin High School** 

Brooklin, ON



# PERSONAL PROJECTS AND ACHIEVEMENTS

#### Made a personal AI assistant

Using python modules, I constructed an Alexa/Google Home like assistant

# Canadian Computing Competition

I competed in the CCC in high school twice where I was met with problems I had to analyze and solve in a quick and effective manner

## Working with Arduinos and open source components

Have worked on several projects (robots as well as other sensor oriented systems) using Arduinos and other hardware modules to create an effective line of communication between the software and hardware

#### Al implementation

Have successfully been able to implement OpenAls Al software into my everyday projects using Python

#### **SKILLS**

#### Tools

 ${\sf Java} \cdot {\sf C++} \cdot {\sf Python} \cdot {\sf HTML} \cdot {\sf JavaScript} \cdot \\$ 

CSS · Excel (VBA) • SQL

#### **Operating Systems**

Windows · Linux

# NOTABLE COMPLETED COURSES

- ✓ Data Structures
- ✓ Sci. Data Analytics
- ✓ Business Analytics
- ✓ Software Design & Analysis
- Computational Science
- Physics I and II
- ✓ Calculus I and II